

Bryan Ortiz Franco

Student CMD

CONTACT

Location: Haarlem

EMAIL: brian.ortiz.franco@hva.nl

ABOUT ME

I am Bryan Ortiz Franco, a Web designer/Developer.

I am 22 years old and live in Haarlem. Since 2021, I have been studying Communication, Multimedia and Design. Before this, I earned my degree in a course in Web development and graphic design. This allowed me to teach my fellow students about Adobe tools within my capabilities.

I'm also a sporty person, I go almost every day, and in my free time I like to take online courses to broaden my knowledge.

DESIGN SKILLS

Adobe Illustrator	90%
Adobe Indesign	80%
Adobe Photoshop	80%
Adobe Premiere Pro	70%
Adobe XD	70%
Blender	40%
Figma	70%
Sketch	40%

CODING SKILLS

HTML & CSS	90%
Javascript	40%
C++	30%

INTEREST









Gaming

Designing

Exercising



LANGUAGE







EDUCATION

2021 - Current

Communication and Multimedia Design Hogeschool van Amsterdam

2018 - 2021

All-round DTP ROC van Amsterdam

2016 - 2017

Business Administration Nova College Haarlem

INTERNSHIP

2020 - 2021

All-round DTP Internship, 3rd year Triple M, Amsterdam

2019 - 2020

All-round DTP Internship, 2nd year Grafix reclame/ Copy-Stop, Amsterdam

2013

Administration Internship VLZS BV, Zwanenburg

WORK EXPERIENCE

2021 - Current

CMD Student Assistant Hogeschool van Amsterdam

2022

Video Editing XTRN

2021

UI Webdesign CTRL Care

2019 - 2020

Illustration Design/ Photo Editing Copy-Stop, Amsterdam-Centrum

2018 - 2019

Shop Assistent Perry Sport, Haarlem